Now this wall here, which is actually a wall that covers up the entrance to the restrooms; this is the wall that we're going to be showing the painting from beginning to end for this particular filming.
So here, again, we're going to have a hilltop.
We're going to have another tiger sitting on this hilltop against rocks, and the water opening up into lakes behind him.
So understand, at this point this is a very, very, very rough sketch.
I'm not looking for accuracy; I'm just looking for ideas.
So I've also now decided how to get rid of this corner in the wall.
I'm going to paint a tree coming up so it takes up the whole of that corner.
And then this tree will carry a fruit, probably mangoes.
I like the idea of mangoes, because mangoes are a fruit that honor the god Ganesha, the Indian elephant god.
And then I think I'm also going to take another tree up this corner, again with mango fruit hanging down from it.
And I'll probably extend that all the way through the rest of the mural with an idea of trees.
So what you have is this very strong foreground with the tigers and the flowers and the tree, and again, all the flowers with the tiger.
I'm thinking I might put a baby tiger in here as well, so that it looks like mother and baby together and then the tree again.
And then everything else fades off into the distance.
So then we have the powerful images in the foreground: the two tigers, the baby tiger, all the hilltops covered wild, beautiful flowers, the two mango trees.
It's very strong in detail in the foreground, including the tiger here that we're going to use for this particular project.
And then everything else slowly fades out into the snowcapped mountains in the background and the blue, cloudy sky to give a feeling of depth.
Like whoever is eating in the restaurant will feel like they're looking out into the distance and into the mountains.
So this is, as I said, a very rough sketch.
The next thing that I will do is come up with a few more ideas, and then I will do another rough sketch which I will present to the owner for him to have a visual idea of what the whole thing is going to look like.
And then I will wait for his reaction to that.